Ariel Strayer

Managerial And Education

Motivated manager with 15 years of experience successfully serving customers in busy, Americana restaurants. Offering in-depth knowledge of craft beers and wine. Recognized for significantly increasing guest check averages by promoting appetizers, specialty items and wine selections. Fast procedural learner with high attention to detail. Looking to apply my skills to a new career.

Work History

2016-04 -2019-05

General Manager And Server

Shelly's Breakfast, Lunch, Diner & Lounge, Burien, Washington

- Resolved guest and employee complaints to maintain complete customer satisfaction and workforce effectiveness.
- Trained incoming staff on restaurant's practices, culture and procedures to maximize job satisfaction and productivity.
- Performed complete opening, closing and shift change duties to keep restaurant working efficiently and teams ready to meet customer needs.
- Shared knowledge of menu items and flavors, enabling customers to make personal decisions based on taste and interest.
- Communicated with employees to prepare schedules in a way to maximize morale and keep within projected hours.
- Managed payroll and communicated with accountant.
- Memorized menu details and prices to hand write and total tickets for personal sales upwards of \$2,400.
- Ref. Adam Hicks (206)661-3642.

2015-07 -2016-06

Preschool Teacher

Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center, Seattle, Washington

- Managed eight two-year-olds.
- Fostered reasoning and problem solving through active exploration games and activities.

Personal Info

Address

SeaTac, WA, 98198

Phone

(206) 388-6228

E-mail

arielbs1991@gmail.com

Skills

Able to improvise in high pressure situations



Able to prioritize tasks efficiently



Communication skills



Able to de-escalate when conflicts arise



Delegation of tasks with clear, detailed instructions



Management and retention of resources



Very Good

Low-pressure sales maximization. Ensuring

- Observed children to identify individuals in need of additional support and developed strategies to improve assistance.
- Promoted physical, academic and social development by implementing diverse classroom and outside activities.
- Monitored students' academic, social and emotional progress and recorded in individual files.
- Consulted with parents to build and maintain positive support networks and support continuing education strategies.
- Gave one-on-one attention to children while maintaining overall focus on entire group.
- Maintained well-controlled classrooms by clearly outlining standards and reinforcing positive behaviors.
- Ref. Sue Tregerman stregerman@hutchkids.org

Education

2013-10

2009-09 - Bachelor of Arts: Psychology

University of Washington - Seattle, WA

- Recipient of Husky Promise Scholarship
- Dean's List Spring 2010 and Winter 2012
- Coursework in Biology, Animal Behavior and Sociobiology
- Five quarters of undergraduate research
- Extensive experience using Microsoft Office (Word, Powerpoint, Excel and Publisher)

2005-09 - High School Diploma 2009-05

Highline High School - Burien, WA

- Awarded World Language Student of the Year 2009
- Member of National Honor's Society
- District qualifier in wrestling, shotput, and discus throwing
- Graduated with 3.8 GPA

customers feel that they have made the right consumer decisions

Very Good

I create a pleasant, comfortable work atmosphere

Excellent

Matlab



Excel



Powerpoint



Word



Payroll



Presentations



Problem-solving skills



Scheduling

